Github提供了很多工具来帮助你管理项目。
Github provides a lot of tools to help you manage projects.
让我们来看看它们是如何工作的
So let's take a look at how they work.
这里有一些你可以用来组织事情的工具
Here's some of the tools available to you to organize things.
现在，第一项是贡献者。
Now, the 1st is contributors.
你可以邀请其他人和你一起完成你的项目。
You can invite others to work alongside you on your project.
这就是Github的特别之处。
That's really what makes Github special.
你也可以制造问题，
You can also create issues,
它允许您创建关于您的项目的笔记，可以由其他人共享和评论。
which allow you to create notes about your projects that can be shared and commented by others.
它们通常是用来解决你需要解决的问题
They're usually for things that you need to fix.
有几种方法可以组织问题
There's a couple of ways that you can organize issues.
一种是用标签来帮助识别问题的目的
One is with labels that help identify the purpose of the issue.
您可以添加这些标签中的一个或多个
You can add one or more of these labels.
里程碑用于分组问题和需要实现的目标
The milestones are for grouping issues and to goals that need to be achieved.
最后，项目是查看工作进度的一种方式
Finally, projects are a way to take a look at the progress of your work
看看你完成目标的情况如何。
and see how well you are accomplishing your goals.
让我们来看看这些
Let's take a look at these.
现在我又回到了项目中，
Here I am back on the project,
我想做的第一件事就是邀请一位撰稿人。
and the 1st thing I want to do it is invite a contributor.
这是一个私人项目，
This is a private project,
我要进入设置，向下滚动，管理访问权限。
so I'm going to go into settings and scroll down to manage access.
在这里 你可以让应用程序重新输入你的密码
Here, you may get apps to rettype your password.
现在你可以看到我还没有邀请任何人
Now you can see here that I haven't invited anyone quite yet.
点击邀请合作者，
I'm going to hit invite a collaborator,
我想邀请我的朋友特里·达克尔
and I want to invite my friend Terry Dactle.
你可以试着在这里输入名字，
So you can try typeping in the name right here,
你可以在这里看到他。
and you can see him right here.
你可以试着输入这个人的用户名，
You can try typing the person s user name,
如果你知道，或者他们的电子邮件地址。
if you know it, or their email address.
我将继续点击这个人并将Terry添加到这个存储库中
I'm going to go ahead and click on this person and add Terry to this repository.
你会发现它的待定邀请减少了，
You'll see that it's less pending invite,
这意味着特里应该收到一封邀请他参加这个项目的邮件。
and that means that Terry should have gotten an email with an invitation to this project.
现在 如果特里没有邀请函 它实际上只是一个项目的链接
Now, if Terry doesn't have that invitation, it's really just a link to the project.
所以你也可以进入团队，把项目的链接粘贴给他们，
So you can just also get into teams and paste the link to the project to them,
他们就能钻进去。
they'll be able to get into them.
让我们从特里的角度来看这个问题
Let's take a look at this from terry's perspective.
Terry收到了一封这样的邮件，所以现在如果我从邮件中进入url，
Terry has received an email like this, so now if I go to the url from the email,
我可以点击“接受邀请”，然后我就可以看到这个泰瑞了。
I can click on accept invitation, and I'll be able to see this as Terry.
现在 让我们继续讨论问题 我要创建一个新问题
Now, let's go ahead and go into issues, and I'm going to create a new issue.
假设我是Terry 我浏览了一下网站 发现了这个问题
Let's say that as Terry, I have taken a look at the website, and I noticed the problem.
所以我听不到所有页面标题的变化
So I couldn't hear change titles on all pages.
哈利看了网站之后，
Since Harry reviewed the website,
他注意到标题只在index.HTML页面上改变了。
and he noticed that the title was only changed on the index.HTML page.
从这里开始 我可以把这个问题分配给组里的一个人
From here, I can assign this issue to a person in the group.
我可以点击这里 把它分配给RabydeLobos
So I can click right here and assign this to Raby de Lobos.
我也可以把它分配给我自己，
I can also assign it to myself,
你可以把这个分配给不止一个人，
so you can assign this to more than one person,
然后我可以添加一些标签。
and then I can add a few labels.
这在技术上可能是个bug 你可以分配多个东西
So this is technically maybe a bug, and you can assign more than one thing.
也许我应该加上这个invalid 因为这看起来不太对
Maybe I'll add this invalid, because this doesn't seem quite right.
这些标签允许你通过标签搜索不同的项目，
And these labels allow you to search different projects by the labels,
通过标签很容易就能看出问题所在。
and it just makes it easy to see what the problems are by looking at the labels.
我要提交这个新问题，
I am going to submit this new issue,
当我们在项目中添加新东西时，你可以看到我们所做的事情的历史。
and you can see a history of what we're doing as we add new things into the project.
让我们在另一个浏览器上看看这个
So let's take a look at this back on my other browser.
我们现在进入问题栏，
We'll go into the issues tab now,
我们会看到我们从特里那里得到了一个问题。
and we'll see that we got an issue from Terry.
让我们来看看这个问题 我在这里加一个评论
So let's take a look at that issue, and I'll add a comment here.
好的，我要在这里评论一下，
All right, so I'm gonna comment in here,
我可以修改它，创造一个里程碑。
and I can modify this and create a milestone.
所以我要添加一个里程碑，
So I'm going to add a milestone,
你可以在这里输入一些东西。
and you can just type in something in here.
我把这称为最后的回顾
I'll call this one final review here.
里程碑是对不同问题进行分组的方式，
And the milestones are ways of grouping a number of different issues,
所以如果你有很多问题，
so if you have a lot of issues,
在最后的复习中，你们需要注意其中的一组，
and theres a group of them that you need to take care of for this final review,
然后你可以给他们分配一个里程碑，对吧?
then you can assign them on milestone, right?
我们再试一次
So let's go ahead and try that again.
我应该在这里按回车键 这为最后的回顾增加了一个里程碑
I should have hit enter here, and that adds now a milestone for this final review.
看 这给我的工作增添了新的历史
And look, it gives me an additional history to what I'm doing.
在这里 你可以看到有两个参与者对这个问题发表了评论
Right here. You can see that there's two participants that have made comments to this issue.
这很好。现在，我注意到网站上有很多活动，
So that's great. Now, I'm noticing that there's quite a bit of activity going on on the website,
真的不是很多。
really not a ton.
但也许现在是在这里创建一个项目的好时机
But maybe this is a good time to create a project here.
我要进入项目部分 点击创建项目
So I'm going to go into the project section and hit create a project.
我给它起个名字 这将是第一个版本的项目
I'll give this a name. This will be the project for the 1st release.
我喜欢在这里选择一个模板
I like to pick a template here.
Github为您提供了许多预构建的项目模板
Github gives you a lot of pre built project templates.
我真的很喜欢这个自动化看板。
I really like this automated Kanban.
看板是敏捷方法的一部分，
Kanban boards are part of the agile methodology,
它们是一种看待待办事项的二维方式。
and they're sort of a two-dimensional way of looking at to-dos.
有人选择这个，然后点击创建项目?
Someone to choose this, and I'll hit create project, right?
你可以看到，当我创建一个项目时，
So you can see that when I created a project,
它让我知道我可以在这里添加纸牌。
it's letting me know that I can add cards here.
我可以添加的其中一辆车是基于我之前创建的问题
And one of the cars that I can add is based on the issue that I created earlier.
这里也有很多说明 你可以读一下
There's also a lot of instructions here, and you can read those.
我要把它们处理掉，
I'm just gonna get rid of them,
我要添加这个问题或者这张卡通过把它拖到这里的这个部分。
and I'm going to add this issue or this card by dragging it into this section right here.
我可以了结这件事。
I can close this out.
您可以看到，您可以添加额外的列。
You can see that you can add additional columns.
默认情况下，我喜欢这三组列
I like these three sets of columns by default
你可以选择一个问题或一张卡，在你需要做的事情的状态上，
you can choose an issue or a card to be on either the state of something that you need to do,
正在进行的事情，或者已经完成的事情。
something that's in progress, or something that's done.
既然我说过我会马上处理这件事 我就把它移到进行中
Since I said I was gonna take care of this right away, I'm gonna move this to in progress.
让我们回过头来看这个问题
Let's go back into the issue and take a look at that.
你可以看到所有这些更新
And you can see that all those updates
我通过创建一个项目和移动东西所做的事情也改变了这个问题。
that I have done by creating a project and moving things around has modified what's happening with this issue as well.
这很方便。
And that's pretty handy.
现在，你可以对问题做更多的事情，
Now, there's a lot more that you can do with issues,
但你可以看到，通过给问题项目加上标签，把事情组织成里程碑之类的东西，
but you can see that by adding labels to issues projects and organizing things into things like milestones,
这真的让创建项目比自己记住所有东西要好得多。
really makes creating projects way better than trying to remember everything by yourself.